[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movie does Rebecca De Mornay play a nanny who tries to steal another womans family?", "correct_answer": "The Hand That Rocks the Cradle", "incorrect_answers": ["Backdraft", "Never Talk to Strangers", "Risky Business"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Benito Mussolini, Napoleon Bonaparte, Alexander the Great, and Julius Caesar were all afraid of these animals.", "correct_answer": "Cats", "incorrect_answers": ["Dogs", "Horses", "Mice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brown sugar, a type of unrefined or partially refined soft sugar, generally has a lower caloric value than white sugar.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Will and Grace, Will was a fine lawyer. What was his last name?", "correct_answer": "Truman", "incorrect_answers": ["Walker", "McFarland", "Adler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Devils on Horseback is a type of food.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Ricks last name in the 1942 movie set during World War II, Casablanca?", "correct_answer": "Blaine", "incorrect_answers": ["Renault", "Marcus", "Donaldson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the biggest number of transplanted organs in a person.", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["7", "2", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the rating for the film Little Miss Sunshine?", "correct_answer": "R", "incorrect_answers": ["G", "PG-13", "PG"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I Love You a Bushel and a Peck was a popular song in the 1950s. How much is a bushel and a peck?", "correct_answer": "ten dry gallons", "incorrect_answers": ["ten meters", "thirty-two gallons", "ten tons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Napoleon Dynamite, what is the name of the girl Pedro is going to build a cake for?", "correct_answer": "Summer Wheatley", "incorrect_answers": ["Wendy Wheatley", "Summer Winston", "Wendy Winston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In ufology, how many kinds of close encounters are there in J. Allen Hyneks classification system for observation and interaction with extraterrestrial intelligence within 150 meters (500 feet)?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "4", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did the U.S.A. launch the Galileo space probe?", "correct_answer": "to explore Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["to explore Pluto", "to explore Mercury", "to explore the sun"]}]